This guy invites the stage,
he's so welcome.
I fall into the world.
Today is the forty-ninth.
Face
Thanks.
I have this little bag of cocoa show here to sell truffle.
In fact,
my backpack broke and I was sad to spend my backpacks too much,
so I'm using this backpack here to travel,
bro.
Good thing I brought 1 banana.
Never eat at the airport.
When I was a teenager,
I always wanted to go to marketing college,
you know,
I never had any money and being invited to give
lectures through my ideas is 1 thing that really fills me up.
Speak caraca,
bro.
I got it right now.
You know,
Song,
from what I got on the plane,
I already slept,
man,
I'm exhausted,
it's on.
Look at the car the bro brought them to me,
old man.
Like, chevos
the event here seems to be pretty cool,
bro.
So, man,
how is it?
Okay, okay, Caio,
how's it going?
All right, man, I'm great.
Thank God.
People asked to look for you to see if everything is ok for the lecture.
The video is playing,
is it playing great bro?
I wrote down 1 collar to have a guide in my talk and I forgot her bro,
you have to do everything improvised.
Now
yeah,
I came here in the parking lot because I
have TDH and I need to pass on the text,
then the guy keeps talking and then I think about my text,
then I think about the guy who's talking,
then I think about the snack.
Brother,
you are the guy.
No matter how much you do,
the best you do is there going to be people who will applaud you,
there will be people who will fuck you,
no matter how good you are.
So make that next speaker.
He's a guy out of class,
okay?
Be inspired if this guy invites the stage,
he falls into the world.
Bora is us,
man.
We're fifty six.
You gotta love it.
I just tô
doing the lecture here,
but I stopped to talk to you.
I think I'm having a good time.
I'm not even sure if there are people,
are you liking them?
It's worth it thanks,
bro.